# Takayasu Nasu

2870 East Broadway Vancouver BC V6R2B6 / Tel: +1(604)376-2691 / E-mail: taka.beckham@gmail.com

Github: https://github.com/TakayasuNasu / portfolio: https://www.i-nasu.com/ / App Store: https://apps.apple.com/us/app/queens-game/id1575671780

### **Profile**

Senior Full-Stack Web Developer with more than 10 years of experience in Information Technology Industry. Experience In Requirements Definition, System Design, Development And Testing For Various Applications Like Client Server, Web Applications IOS Application, Android Application.

### **Skills**

JavaScript	<ul> <li>TypeScript</li> </ul>	• React	• Vue.js	• Anguler.js	• Node.js	<ul> <li>JQuery</li> </ul>	Next.js
<ul> <li>Swift</li> </ul>	<ul> <li>Java</li> </ul>	<ul><li>PHP</li></ul>	<ul> <li>Python</li> </ul>	<ul> <li>Ruby</li> </ul>	<ul><li>HTML</li></ul>	<ul><li>CSS</li></ul>	<ul> <li>SCSS</li> </ul>
<ul> <li>Wordpress</li> </ul>	<ul> <li>Laravel</li> </ul>	<ul> <li>CakePhp</li> </ul>	<ul> <li>Rails</li> </ul>	<ul> <li>Graphql</li> </ul>	<ul> <li>MySql</li> </ul>	<ul> <li>SQLite</li> </ul>	<ul> <li>Apache</li> </ul>
<ul> <li>Nginx</li> </ul>	<ul> <li>Docker</li> </ul>	<ul> <li>Git/Github</li> </ul>	• AWS	<ul> <li>CircleCI</li> </ul>			

# **Work Experience**

### Full Stack Developer - Massive Media Inc. / Vancouver, Canada (October 2021 - May 2023)

- Responsible for front/back end design, implementation, testing and debugging.
- Created corporate website with project managers and designers.

#### Lead Front End Developer (Contract) - DPCode Inc. / Vancouver, Canada (May 2021 - August 2021)

- · Mentoring members, managing tasks, One-on-one meetings, and reviewing their sources. My team has 6 people including me.
- Front end requirements definition, spec design, implementation.

#### Full Stack Developer / Technical Director - Medix inc. / Tokyo, Japan (June 2017 - August 2020)

- Created SPA for centralized management which useful knowledge within the company that was stored in various locations. That SPA is made with Docker, Laravel, Graphql and Vue.js.
- · As project leader, I selected technologies and supported members of the project team.

### Senior Web Developer - Strawbag inc. / Tokyo, Japan (November 2014 - October 2016)

- Created a CI system that combined Bitbucket, Wercker, and Slack to support development when I built a job-search management site.
- Cooperated and built some web applications with the Chinese coworker. That's when I supported him by creating task management, specification explanations, sample code, and documentation.

### Junior Web Developer - BTM inc. / Tokyo, Japan (April 2013 - October 2014)

- · Continued to release Smartphone game which over 100 php files, built with over 100 tables, used by over 10,000 people daily consistently.
- Created Android application that uses polymorphism in its design which is made with Java and I manage team tasks.

### Junior Web Developer - I-Freek / Fukuoka, Japan (June 2012 - March 2013)

· Modified an existing program made with Perl and deploy it on Linux while checking the Apache conf file with Vim.

### **Projects**

### Primasun - https://www.primasun.com/ (September 2022 - February)

- Tech Stack: React/TypeScript/Gatsby/Contentful/Netlify
- Designed Contentful Types to update large portions of the site without code modification
- The site was well received by the client. It led to a contract to support social media management.

### Packetlabs - https://www.packetlabs.net/ (October 2021 - March 2022)

- Tech Stack: React/TypeScript/Gatsby/Contentful/Netlify
- · Improved website performance by 20-30 points through understanding and use of Gatsyb and Contentful features

#### Dpcode Academy - https://dpcode.academy (May 2021 - August 2021)

- Tech Stack: React/Next.js/Cognito/Api Gateway/DynamoDB/scss
- · People who want to study computer science, algorithms, and something like that can sign up for online classes from this site.
- · Students can know which lectures they have attended, and the instructor can control the content and duration of the lectures.

#### S-Portal (Jun 2019 - August 2020)

- Tech Stack: Vue/SPA/Graphql/Laravel/Docker
- · SPA for centralized management of knowledge related to site production, accessed daily by 80% of all employees

### FeedLP (January 2018 - September 2019) - https://www.itstaffing.jp/lp/fd008/?mfeed=D210310647D

- Tech Stack: React/Go/AWS Fargate/Docker/MySql
- We made an API for the job information used in the feed ads and used React to display it dynamically. The UI is now ready to be updated without any work on the server-side.

### Original CMS (November 2014 - September 2016)

- Tech Stack: php/Laravel/Slim/Phalcon/Cakephp/Zend/Smarty/MySql/JQuery/JavaScript
- Creation of portal sites for group companies and renewal of architect office sites
- https://www.pharmaproduct.co.jp/
- https://mynavi-job20s.jp/

### Web browser Social game applications (January 2014 - October 2014)

- Tech Stack: php/Smarty/MySql/JavaScript/Jira
- Continued to release Smartphone game which over 100 php files, built with over 100 tables, used by over 10,000 people daily consistently.

## Education